Excellent. All right, enjoy.
太棒了。好的，慢慢享用。
Could you ever see automating the decorating of these donuts?
你觉得将来这些甜甜圈的装饰过程有可能实现自动化吗？
We find that the best way to drive efficiency is with the core-shell donut or the ring.
我们发现，提高效率最好的方式，是生产基础款甜甜圈（圆环甜甜圈）。
But when it comes to putting the finishing touches on our donuts, that complexity requires the hands and the eye coordination of our Krispy Kremers.
但是，说到给甜甜圈做最后的装饰，这种复杂的工作还是需要 Krispy Kreme 员工的双手和手眼协调能力。
Plus a robot could squish them, right?
而且机器人还有可能把它们压扁，对吧？
I would be very worried about squishing the donuts.
我会非常担心把甜甜圈压坏。
After a period of missed sales targets and profit losses, Krispy Kreme is looking for ways to grow.
经历了一段未达销售目标和利润亏损之后，Krispy Kreme 正在寻找新的增长方式。
That means pushing its donut-making machines to do more and more.
这意味着不断提高甜甜圈生产设备的工作能力。
But even here, automation has its limits.
但即使是在这里，自动化也是有局限性的。
While machines can mix and glaze a standard donut, they still struggle with seasonal and limited-time designs.
虽然机器可以完成标准甜甜圈的搅拌和裹糖，但面对季节限定或限时款设计，它们仍然力不从心。
We have piloted a couple of robot-style solutions to see if they would work, but it got super messy.
我们试验过几种机器人方案，看看是否可行，但最后现场一团糟。
The glaze got into the joints of the robots.
糖浆流进了机器人的关节里。
It's pretty tough to not harm the quality of the donut, and that's the most important thing for us.
要在不影响甜甜圈品质的情况下实现自动化非常困难，而品质对我们来说才是最重要的。
Oh, look, there's the donuts.
哦，看，那就是甜甜圈。
Yeah, this is one of our largest lines that we operate across the country.
这是我们在全国运营的最大生产线之一。
It can make 400 dozen donuts an hour.
它每小时可以生产 400 打甜甜圈。
More than 50% of the donuts we sell are our original glaze.
我们销售的甜甜圈中，有超过一半都是经典糖霜款。
So it's absolutely critical that we get this process right.
因此，把这个流程做到准确无误至关重要。
How many unusable donuts do you tend to have?
通常会产生多少不能出售的甜甜圈？
So what we do is, we try and aim for over 93% efficiency.
我们的目标是达到超过93%的生产效率。
We obviously do make sure that the donut has to be perfect.
我们当然一定会确保每个甜甜圈都是完美的。
We really care about quality a lot.
我们非常重视产品质量。
I just saw one got taken off.
我刚刚看到有一个被拿走了。
It looked a little sad.
它看起来有点"不太行"。
It's really important that they retain the perfect shape.
保持完美的外形非常重要。
What would you say the biggest bottleneck is currently in these manufacturing facilities?
你认为目前这些工厂最大的瓶颈是什么？
Making sure that as we change flavors, we're setting the teams up for success.
确保每次更换口味时，我们都能让团队顺利完成生产。
The fact that we still have that hand-decorated element allows us to be incredibly agile as a business.
保留人工装饰这个环节，使我们的企业能够保持极高的灵活性。
And offer a huge variety for our guests.
并为顾客提供丰富多样的产品。
But it is costly, right?
但成本确实很高，对吧？
It is costly, but it's definitely worth it.
确实成本高，但绝对值得。
Krispy Kreme has more than 6,500 employees across the US, and about 10% to 15% of them work as decorators.
Krispy Kreme在全美拥有超过 6,500 名员工，其中大约 10% 到 15% 从事甜甜圈装饰工作。
Each can decorate up to 50 dozen donuts per hour.
每个人每小时最多可以装饰 50 打甜甜圈。
[和员工对话] What's the hardest part of your job?
[和员工对话] 你工作中最困难的部分是什么？
The hardest part, the demand.
最困难的就是需求量。
Yeah, it'd be the demand, 'cause sometimes you have a lot to make.
对，应该就是需求量，因为有时候要做的甜甜圈非常多。
I see these ladies have, like, so many donuts they're making, but sometimes you have to have a whole lot.
我看到这些女士手头正在做很多甜甜圈，但有时候需要制作的数量真的特别大。
Depending on how popular the donut is, it really sells a whole lot.
根据这种甜甜圈受欢迎的程度，有些款式确实能卖出很多。
And part of that is because you have so many limited-time offers, right?
其中一部分原因是你们推出了很多限时产品，对吧？
Yes, yes. Limited-time offers and sales, they merge together and people are like, "Hey, donuts."
对，对。限时产品和促销活动叠加在一起，人们就会想："嘿，有甜甜圈。"
Do you think your job could be automated ever?
你觉得你的工作有一天可能实现自动化吗？
Could it be automated?
它能实现自动化吗？
I mean, to an extent maybe.
我的意思是，或许在一定程度上可以。
But all the different things that we do on top of the donut, I don't think a machine could do that.
但是我们在甜甜圈表面进行的各种不同装饰，我觉得机器做不到。
Doesn't do it with love.
机器不会带着爱去做。
There's no love in that.
那里面没有爱。
Robot can't do that.
机器人做不到。
Not at all, I don't think so.
完全做不到，我不这么认为。
[Narrator] But Krispy Kreme is under pressure to become more efficient.
[Narrator] 但 Krispy Kreme 正面临提高效率的压力。
The company is still fighting to remain out of the red after its ambitious deal to sell donuts at McDonald's fell apart.
在与麦当劳合作销售甜甜圈的雄心勃勃的协议破裂后，公司仍在努力避免再次陷入亏损。
[和Manager对话问答] Let's talk about McDonald's.
[和Manager对话问答] 我们来谈谈麦当劳。
What happened with that?
那次合作发生了什么？
I think that the consumer was really looking for more convenient access to Krispy Kreme's fresh donuts, and the partnership with McDonald's was designed to enable that, and certainly started effectively.
我认为消费者确实希望能够更方便地买到 Krispy Kreme 的新鲜甜甜圈，而与麦当劳的合作正是为了满足这一需求，并且合作最初的确进展顺利。
However, we found that the revenue streams weren't necessarily sustainable over time because the conditions weren't as optimum as we have with many of our other customers.
然而，我们发现这些收入来源未必能够长期持续，因为相关条件不如我们与许多其他客户合作时那样理想。
Let's get more into the nuts and bolts.
我们来进一步谈谈具体细节。
I know you manufacture a lot of your own equipment.
我知道你们很多设备都是自行制造的。
It's kind of unusual.
这有点不同寻常。
How precise are these machines?
这些机器的精确度有多高？
Well, I mean, I think there is always an element of the human element to make sure they run well.
嗯，我的意思是，我认为其中始终需要一定程度的人工参与，才能确保机器良好运转。
But yeah, they can do, one of our lines, a standard line, does 200 dozen donuts an hour.
不过，是的，我们的一条标准生产线每小时能生产 200 打甜甜圈。
We have ones that can do all the way up to 400 dozen.
我们有些生产线的产能甚至可以达到 400 打。
You do have to keep an eye on many of the temperatures and humidity, and making sure the yield of these machines is working effectively.
你确实必须密切关注不同环节的温度和湿度，并确保这些机器的产出效率保持良好。
I always think that our Krispy Kreme employees bring something special to our donuts.
我始终认为，Krispy Kreme 的员工为我们的甜甜圈赋予了一些特别的东西。
I do think that there's opportunity to improve and become more efficient.
我的确认为，我们仍有改进和提高效率的空间。
I do think we can leverage technology, and we're exploring various things, whether it's in the manufacturing process or in distribution, demand planning, supply planning, the like, where we can leverage technology.
我确实认为我们可以利用技术，目前也正在探索多种方案，无论是在生产流程、配送、需求规划、供应规划，还是其他类似领域，我们都可以借助技术。
But I'm really proud of what our Krispy Kreme does too.
不过，我也非常为 Krispy Kreme 员工所做的工作感到骄傲。
Where would you say you are in your turnaround story right now?
你认为公司目前处于业务转型进程的哪个阶段？
Yeah, we've been growing the brand.
是的，我们一直在推动品牌增长。
Krispy Kreme is a growth story for many years.
多年来，Krispy Kreme 一直是一个持续增长的品牌。
We implemented a turnaround in the middle of last year because we wanted to make sure that growth was behind sustainable revenue streams, profitable, and that we strengthened our balance sheet.
我们在去年年中实施了转型计划，因为我们希望确保增长建立在可持续的收入来源之上，能够带来利润，同时增强公司的资产负债表。
And you are forecasting a profitable year this year?
你们预计今年会实现盈利吗？
We are, we're forecasting 2% to 4% system-wide sales growth.
是的，我们预计全系统销售额将增长 2% 到 4%。
And to drive up margins as we have been, we've seen margins go up 250 basis points so far since we implemented the turnaround.
同时，为了继续提高利润率，自实施转型以来，我们目前已经看到利润率上升了 250 个基点。
We expect to continue to see that margin improvement, all as we shift to a more capital-like model, franchising becoming a bigger part of the revenue stream, so that we can continue to grow, but in a more capital-efficient way.
随着我们转向一种资本投入更轻的模式，并让特许经营成为收入来源中更重要的一部分，我们预计利润率将继续改善，从而能够以资本效率更高的方式持续增长。
What is the future for donuts in this kind of health-conscious GLP-1 era?
在这样一个注重健康、GLP-1 药物盛行的时代，甜甜圈的未来会怎样？
What I think our customers are looking for when it comes to donuts is great quality, great tasting, fresh donuts, and that's what Krispy Kreme does.
我认为，说到甜甜圈，我们的顾客真正想要的是品质出色、美味而且新鲜的产品，而这正是 Krispy Kreme 所提供的。
You know, when you have your moment of sweet treat sharing, it's gotta be worth it, it's gotta be amazing.
你知道，当你享受并分享甜食的那一刻，它必须值得，也必须足够美妙。
And that's why I think our donuts really, even in this changing world, are relevant.
这就是为什么我认为，即使在这个不断变化的世界里，我们的甜甜圈依然具有吸引力和存在价值。